3,2,1
start!
Cute! Cute!
cute!
Wow! It's shrimp!
It's shrimp, so there's a lot of it.
Cute pouch, what is that?
And today's
Made by Yame-chan
Hits are so cute, cat
cute
I wore this before and it's cute
Today, the catering was decorated with a huge number of events.
It felt a little more luxurious than usual and it felt like the end of the year.
I ate cake
I ate it, it was delicious
It was delicious
by
Oh, is that okay?
What's the point?
What's the point today?
I let my hair down a little
So cute! Peter with bangs
That's right, I made it a little heavier.
I like anime and manga
I'm doing it as a character
I tried to imitate it a little
cute
lol
It might be embarrassing to do it alone
I'll enjoy having this
Can I eat it if I change my dinner?
please
I don't seem to have any interest in blooming.
Today's hair is up
It's so big and we're facing each other.
Yeah
Which one is better?
what?
No, wait
Love so love love
This is also lovey-dovey
Eh, lovey-dovey
I see that same face though
We're looking at the same face
Is that an explosion?
love love jankou
thank you
It's gonna be warm
Ah, ah
When there is a lot of static electricity
Of course
While giggling every time
It hurt
Then please close it.
Bybee
Last opening of the year
bye bye
Huh?
ah!
I guess I'll go then
Well then
What should I do?
1 piece
Yeah
What should I do if they don't pull me out?
1 piece
good
oh
Wow
It's early
Is there anything left?
It's true
picture
a
Is there a feeling like that?
picture
It seems like a card that can be exchanged.
what color
red
good
picture
I put it in
I couldn't say it for a while
amazing
happy
It's delicious
Looks delicious
I put it in.
Wow
yes drone 2
That's why Miku
First of all, without Drone 2
oh
Yes, yes
What is this?
1 piece, 2 pieces, only 1 piece left
It's just begun
8 servings without
Thank you for your hard work
I didn't even put out two.
yes
Thank you for your hard work
One more photo
Okay
copper?
please
good
ah
With 2 pieces out
Well then, nod
terrible!
So much!
Akari!
What a shame!
Yay!
That's what came out
thank you
In front of me are these two people
Eh, isn't it cute?
hey
Everyone
copper?
It's okay
That's fine
bye bye
Now go to the next scene
Let's go
look, flowers
cute
cute cute cute
You look matching today, hair.
Looks sweet
Well, yeah
You copied it, right?
You don't have to imitate this hairstyle.
Miku did it first.
Because everyone is doing it
But I was hooked.
I went to the same makeup shop after Miku.
I had my makeup done by the same makeup artist after Miku.
You did it, right?
That's what it was
Congratulations on getting bored
congratulations
It's rare today.
I'm saying it clearly
Looks like you're good at job hunting
Looks good for job hunting
Impressed by the corporate philosophy of the head office
I have written an entry sheet
Does the fact that the head office is your first choice mean that you are not accepted elsewhere?
yes
a
I feel very serious.
thank you
Thank you very much from now on.
Does that mean it's OK?
Wow, the handshake was already shaken
Does that mean the contract is OK?
yes
cute
congratulations
Iro-chan is also rare.
I put it together
I'm always embarrassed, but
After replacement
I tried my best
I got it
Did something happen to you?
Get it later
this is?
Ah, yes! Look! Panda!
So cute! I got something too
What about the song?
I will receive it later and use it regularly.
Let's do our best!
I'm seriously watching the video at Miku-chan's level.
thank you for your hard work!
Are you tied up today?
cute
Roll it up
wait a minute
cute
Saya is working really hard
lol
Good evening
cute now
You're so cute right now, you can definitely see it right now
Unusual bangs
It's thin today
yes
It's the last one and everyone is doing something unusual.
cute
Seriously cute
What should I do?
Do a cute pose
Ah, I did the same thing
Ah, cute
Please come closer
sound effect
Curon?
Copied
Alone?
Huh?
Ah, so cute!
Cute! So cute!
You want to see that now, right?
You wanted to see it now, right?
It's kind of amazing
once again once again
Look at it like this
What is it?
picture?
still?
not at all
Not at all
I don't understand at all
I want to see it
Sparkling
end
bye bye
Olly Christmas!
Congratulations!
Good for you
thank you!
Yay!
Congratulations!
thank you!
everyone!
Happy new year!
congratulations!
It's 2025!
I'm off to countdown keeping now!
I'm heading over!
I will do my best!
The concept is from children to adults.
me in 2024
in 2025
Amber's Takase from the past 3 years, with bangs like this,
I made her look like a beautiful woman, but then I instantly separated her to make her look more mature.
It's cute.
Squeak!
I have large earrings so you can see them.
I did it
gorgeous
there were
The picture is so cold that I'm worried I won't be able to sleep tonight.
It's really small.
It's perfect for who you are.
lie.
No way. I say she's cute, but I don't have a complex about her.
It's really short.
But that's just the meaning.
What is the yellow thing you see here?
Yes, cheese.
Yes, last. Seino. yes.
2020.
This is the first performance of 2015.
What will you perform?
Hello Kyo.
It's Sionna.
This is Sionna.
It's hand-soaked blue, isn't it?
If I don't leave
Tied my cheeks, pictures of me
Demy Nancent
Nedetermination
picture book
It's starting
It's about to start
Once it starts, it's over quickly
thank you for your hard work
Thank you for watching